[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ theme song]
[Exciting music plays]
[Chaebol man clears his cough]
(Chaebol man) This is my first time seeing your face.
You know me, right?
What, are you a chaebol too?
(Chaebol man) Yes, that’s right, chaebol
If you came alone, would you play with me?
Then I take their stuff or whatever.
It must be a customer, so why are you speaking so briefly?
(Edited) Be polite to customers
Isn’t that what you make a living at? If you’re a chaebol?
[Chaebol Man’s Laughter]
(Chaebol man) Ah, this bitch is funny.
No, just looking at it from before,
I thought it wasn't from our side.
You were a customer, huh?
Okay
I'll treat you like a queen
in bed
[dark music]
Hey, let go
- (Edit) Don’t let it go?
- I liked the angry concept.
(Chaebol man) Do you see one or two things like this?
Stop it and go
[Chaebol man’s pained moans]
[mumbling sound]
Is this really crazy?
[Soft music]
Baby
let's go
[mumbling sound]
[humorous music]
Yes?
[Sujeong’s embarrassed groan]
What?
Am I a baby?
[flashing sound effect]
[Baby laughing sound effect]
(Juyeon) Ah
That's not what I said to you.
What exactly, baby, let’s go
Baby, let's go into the water
That's what I meant
That friend
From the United States, the heat is very intense.
was famous for riding
How is it cool now?
(Chaebol man) Did you turn around?
What is that bitch?
Who is that bitch doing this to me?
employee
(Juyeon) Not just an employee
A very important employee who cannot be missing from the company.
Let's go, Team Leader Baek, it's going to rain soon.
[The sky rumbles]
It looks like a shower
How did you know it was raining?
For telling me
Who?
(Juyeon) When I ask about the weather every morning
I will answer
What an amazing guy.
Sometimes it's better than humans
Ah...
So, did you meet any important customers?
It looks like you didn't attend.
If I knew it was a party like this
I probably wouldn’t have come to the country either.
[Response of correction]
(Edited) Anyway, now
Are you letting me off work?
(Juyeon) No way
Oh, I really want to see you.
(Edited) Is it all you need to provide job security?
Guarantee of basic rights
It's not working, right now.
If you keep not letting me get off work,
Give me some food
Oh, I didn't even have lunch.
Oh, I'm hungry!
Ah, I'm out of energy!
energy
It seems overflowing
[Stomach growling sound]
[flashing sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
(Edited) Look, am I right?
- But why speak informally...
- What?
[light music]
[Humorous sound effects]
(Juyeon) Can this be a meal?
(Edited) Why not?
You have all the coals, right?
Is the menu not that good?
I'm asking too quickly
Do whatever you want
Because you followed me freely
Not if you don’t want to eat it.
You have to eat what you ordered.
Since it's outside, chocolate is really not an option, right?
You only drink espresso.
[Squeaking sound effect]
(Juyeon) I’m choking to death
[Juyeon lightly clears his throat]
[laughter]
(Sujeong) What are you going to do after eating this?
It's all late. How can I monitor it?
Are you not going to sleep?
Or are we going to sleep together?
[ding sound effect]
Oh, you signed a contract.
The manager's personal life
Even if I want to leak it, I can’t.
If you get sued
Do you have any money to ask?
I have a lot of debt to pay off
What is the benefit?
The company with the highest salary
Do you get cut, yes?
(child) Yes!
- (Edited) Huh?
- (Ai Mo) It’s cute.
Yunho, do you like it?
[Humorous sound effects]
(Edited) It’s a pity
Ah, I see you are giving me a doll.
(I Boo) Does Yunho like Tokkeum the best?
[Swooshing sound effect]
[Exciting music]
What should I do with the doll?
Oh, it's cute, and it's free.
Cute...
You mean that?
(Edited) Yes
Isn't it cute?
(Juyeon) Get off work
- (Edited) Yes?
-After eating all of this, I leave work.
Do it
There is no softness
(Edited) Please pack it for me
[surprised gasp]
How much is this?
(Edited) Oh, even if you sell it used, it will be 300.
Still, I have to return it, right?
[humorous music]
Wow
Oh, why not?
Kid...
What if it's expensive?
It's not mine and it won't come off.
[Sujeong’s powerful moans]
Done
[Sound of lights going out]
[Sujeong’s irritated exclamation]
I'm so tired I'm dying
[Sound of door opening]
[lively music]
[Sound of door closing]
[Door lock operating sound]
(Wonseop) Oh, what, did the fire go out?
(Edited) Uh
(Wonseop) Oh my
Wait until daddy gets home, uh
I would do it for you
You can easily do this alone
Now
Hey, now I can pass on something to the store.
(Sujeong) I learned everything to inherit it.
I also got an electrical license.
I'm going to win this
You know that I always go to the reading room after work, right?
By the way, you are my daughter too
Isn't it amazing?
[Wonseop’s happy laughter]
[sound of a switch being pressed]
(Edited) It’s gum.
[Sujeong and Wonseop’s laughter]
[Calm music plays]
(Hajin) It’s a bar, but there aren’t too many customers, right?
It should have a noisy taste.
Is it nice to be quiet?
I also promoted it in person.
It was of no use.
Huh? It's useful
I'm here
I also clicked the heart
- Oh, did you come here after reading the article?
- (Shinwon) Yes
Was it fun? The concept is clear
Write, but
Did you write it yourself?
I don't match well with the boss.
I wrote it myself
I saw people in the past.
[Shinwon’s exclamation and laughter]
[Hajin’s light laughter]
Me, but
The photo was a bit disappointing.
(Shinwon) The food
It's important to look delicious
uh
[camera shutter sound]
Doesn’t it feel good to take pictures like this?
[Hajin’s surprised exclamation]
Composition is important in photos.
Take pictures so that the entire food comes out well
If that's difficult
Take a close photo like this
[surprised elasticity]
[camera shutter sound]
Like this?
Well, there shouldn't be anything else next to it.
- (Shinwon) Like this
- (Hajin) Ah...
- Like this?
- (Identity) No, here it is like this.
[Soft sound effect]
[Exciting music]
(Shinwon) Ah
sorry
Do you want to sleep with me?
[Naughty music]
Is that so?
[Exciting music]
[sigh]
(Juyeon) I think I’m finally going to live now
[alarm sound]
[Shinwon’s tired moans]
What time is it now?
(Hajin) Oh, it’s only 5 o’clock.
sleep more
It's 5 o'clock, where are you going?
To catch fish
(Shinwon) Huh?
[Soft music]
(Hajin) Thank you
I don't even have anything to take you to.
(Shinwon) There’s still time left for work.
Can't I look at it from the side?
Because this is my first time here
I'm going to my parents' store.
Can you afford it?
There's nothing you can't do
Adults think I’m pretty
Then it's a bigger problem
If only I wore pants
There must be a fuss trying to get her to remarry.
Are you divorced?
why?
Are you more excited?
(Shinwon) Uh...
I don’t think I should add anything here?
I have to go to work
[laughter]
Go
Yesterday was fun thanks to you
[sigh]
(Hajin) Mom!
- (Ha Jin-mo) Why are you so late?
- (Hajin) Me?
What are you late for?
I came just in time
(Ha Jin-mo) It’s too late
If you're going to take the goods without any margin
Come early and help out at the store
(Hajin) Uh, did you see that the thief has a conscience?
(Ha Jin-mo) Oh my, I’m proud of this
Oh, by the way, what about your store?
Ha-jeong said there were no customers?
There's nothing you can do if you fail
(Hajin Mo) Oh, just!
You told me to save up alimony and get a job, right?
Oh my, what kind of business are you doing?
I quit the company I was working for
When are you going to get married?
Divorced in less than a year
Oh my, hey
Now it's been less than a year
The store has to close
Ah, why are you like this?
Isn't it thick, huh?
Who do you look like to be so upset?
I only have one man
We've been meeting each other for 10 years
Have you forgotten that you even got married?
Oh my, oh my
[Ha Jin-mo’s frustrated groan]
Dad, what do you like today?
sea bream
Okay
(Edited) Director
This is what I wore yesterday
(Juyeon) Have you dried your hair?
I don't think there was time for that.
Oh, I just wore this for a short time yesterday.
The clothes you wear are clean
Isn’t it obvious?
(Juyeon) It even rained yesterday
This isn't even the clothes I said I would wear?
I thought it was basic courtesy.
My standards are too high
[Interesting music]
(Juyeon) Even so, general education for employees is required.
I thought I needed it
in the elevator
There were people who talked profanely
That's how much I am now
Are you saying this is nonsense?
I think the voices were similar
You can do it.
(Edited) Please cover this as an expense?
[Tickling sound effect]
What is that head shaking, Mr...
[ding sound effect]
[Sound of door closing]
[Soft music]
Oh, look, it's not my style.
It doesn't suit you, does it?
Didn't it suit you?
Liberal arts education?
(Edited) Let’s start by educating ourselves.
Anyway, I just do everything the way I want...
[Humorous sound effects]
[Thumping sound effect]
[humorous music]
(Juyeon) Everything goes as it wants
That's not what I'm talking about, right?
[Humorous sound effects]
Are you overly self-conscious?
[Awkward laughter]
(Edited) Me, me
I'm too selfish
[Junsu and Nana’s awkward laughter]
self-objectification
That one is great
[Sharp sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Swooshing sound effect]
[Sujeong clears her throat in embarrassment]
(Juyeon) Let’s start the meeting.
The importance of this renewal project is
I think everyone knows without saying anything.
Start from Seoul
We plan to expand nationwide.
The beginning is even more important
So the place I chose was Gangnam branch.
Not the main branch, but the Gangnam branch?
Gangnam commercial district is a core consumption area
(Edited) However, compared to other competitors
Our department store sales were especially low.
It's time to explore a new path.
If it fails, the risk will be high, right?
What you will get if you succeed
I think it will be big
(Edited) As long as you break it, sales will increase
Because it’s a guaranteed area.
Of course a little more stable
There are also the following candidates:
Done
I also opened the Gangnam branch from the beginning.
Because I had it in mind
[Exciting music]
There is a consensus, so why waste time?
Let's decide on the Gangnam branch.
yes
(Junsu) Oh, where are you going?
Gangnam branch
(Edited) Because the final candidate has been decided
I need to go and understand the site properly, right?
- (Junsu) I...
- (Nana) What is it?
two minutes
You promised in advance, didn't you?
(Junsu) That’s right
The hands and feet fit together very well, just like that
[bicycle bell sound]
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Soft music]
(Hajin) Do you want to sleep with me?
Is that so?
[Mouse operation sound]
(Shinwon) Oh, Mr.
[Laughing awkwardly] Ah, yes
[Shinwon’s sigh]
[sigh]
[Elegant music plays]
(Juyeon) About the renewal project
You probably heard it before
(Branch Manager) Yes, our branch
I heard it could be the beginning
(Leader) I will be, starting from today
(Branch Manager) Ah, yes
Thank you for your cooperation, branch manager.
yes, you should
By surveying customers
- (Branch Manager) We will begin to understand demand.
- Is that okay?
(Branch manager) Yes?
[Exciting music]
One of the main purposes of renewal is
Acquiring new customers
Even people who are not existing customers
Take a survey so you can participate
the brand they want
Products, services, facilities
We need to get it all right.
(Branch Manager) To people who are not customers
How...
(Juyeon) Anyone wants to participate
Isn’t it okay to just not bother them?
It seems like it's too much
Spend money or anything
Well, there’s no need to save money on something like this.
(Branch Manager) Ah, yes, I will proceed right away.
(Juyeon) Yes, go see it.
Yes? Already?
If you go with the branch manager,
A high-ranking person came
Isn’t this like publicity?
See the scene as it is
I want to understand the problem
(Branch Manager) Yes, then feel free to look around.
We will contact you
Huh?
Here...
(Juyeon) You recognize me, the brand I use
I
[Sound effect taken out]
I only write there
[Humorous sound effects]
My favorite band vocalist
I only use it here
[Juyeon clears his throat]
(Edit) Oh, I see.
I see the last letter of the sign over there
I looked at it because it seemed a little tilted.
[Humorous sound effects]
(Juyeon) Well, you have a good sense of vision.
You don't recognize my sunglasses brand
I'll pass it on to the staff.
(Man) Oh, the sunglasses cost 1 million won.
Does the repair fee of 80 make sense?
[light music]
(Clerk) This is everything from the legs to the single screw.
It's all designed by craftsmen.
To repair a broken part
Send products to head office in Italy
I had to re-deliver it...
(Man) No, that’s still true
This isn't something I'm making again.
Is 80 his name?
(Clerk) Make it again
You are no different.
[Man laughs]
What are you?
[upbeat music]
People who don't understand value don't deserve to wear these sunglasses
None
(Man) [Bewildered] Who are you now?
Now I have qualifications or not, huh?
me?
[Throwing sound effect]
[Flying sound effect]
[Shooting sound effect]
[Eye blinking sound effect]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Exciting music]
the value of the product
someone who understands perfectly
[surprised sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Sound effect of turning away]
(Man) No, it's done, it's done, I don't know
Hey, if you want to come shopping
Go buy something for yourself
Don't piss people off, okay?
Make people angry?
No, this guy!
[Sound effect bouncing]
(Edited) I’m sorry
[humorous music]
[Squeaking sound effect]
How about this?
Than what you used
I think this would be perfect for our guests.
[Laughing] So, in the meantime,
Buy me new sunglasses now?
(Man) These people are now
But are you trying to kill me with a vase?
[Knocking] To this person here
Matching sunglasses...
(Man) What!
[Sound effect bouncing]
(Edited) No, if you want to get after-sales service anyway,
You have to wait a long time
If the value is the same
Still a little more suitable
Buying sunglasses
Isn’t this a reasonable choice?
I am an employee at Yongseong Department Store.
Discounts are also possible
Then it's 650,000 won.
[Flashing sound effect]
How do you feel?
Even if I put it on just a little bit, it's just a little bit like this
A little on the bridge of the nose
Let me show you the mirror.
(Man) Give it to me
[rock music]
[surprised elasticity]
[Humorous sound effects]
It's the best
[light music]
[Humorous sound effects]
[The man clears his cough awkwardly]
Well, then...
Or buy a new one
- (Edited) Oh, is that so?
- (Man) Oh, whatever you buy.
(Edited) Yes, then it will be a new product
Oh my, what's going on?
It's not that I don't know the value of the product.
I guess my wallet was light.
Anyway
What if you deal with customers like that?
Even if you are the head of the department
(Juyeon) That’s right
An unacceptable mistake
I almost committed it
Really, one of the few stains in life
I almost got caught one more time
Baek Soo-jeong blocked it.
Thank you, but...
to that extent
It's my first time seeing a bare face
I didn't recognize you
(Edited) Yes?
who?
Oh, maybe at that concert hall?
You were singing, right?
(Sujeong) [Surprise] Awesome
Why didn’t you pretend to know?
You're a fan
Oh, it was a secret
Oh well, just leave like this.
Are you going to leave it there?
Well, can I at least get your autograph instead?
Done
wait and see
I...
I have a pen...
- (Edited) There is no pen.
- (Juyeon) Here.
[Exciting music]
(Edited) Hey there
Hey there
Wait a minute
I saw a performance once
I'm such a fan
- (Man) Did you?
- (Edited) Just one autograph...
[Man's muttering sound]
I don't know.
Oh, you are so cool.
(Man) Ah, thank you
- (Edited) A photo?
- (Man) Yes
Oh, wait a minute.
(Edited) Director
I told him I was a fan and he said he would take a picture for me.
[Surprising sound effect]
Photo?
(Edited) It would be nice if the head of the department took the picture.
It shouldn't be revealed.
I'll take the picture instead
Be satisfied vicariously
[upbeat music]
[Disapproving sigh]
[Clears cough in disapproval]
I'm taking a picture
(Main role) One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
[Sound of repeatedly pressing camera shutter]
[Eye rolling sound effect]
(Edited) What is this?
I only have hair.
Because I'm not a fan of Baek Soo-jeong.
(Juyeon) Please send photos to Gantalk.
I guess I won't send it away
(Edited) Ah, at most the autograph
They even let me take a picture.
Who treated me like a cold meal?
(Juyeon) That’s right
They even took pictures of me with my autograph.
(Edited) I will decline to say thank you.
(Juyeon) After all, my singer
I thought you were only good at singing
He even has a great personality.
Do you like it that much?
Are you starting a fight?
I'm jealous
(Edited) Do something passionately
That you can like it
I think it's precious.
It's not easy to find something you like.
It's not easy to like for a long time
So
Feel free to like it as much as you like.
[Calm music]
No matter what others think
The former director said he enjoys a hobby.
I don’t think there is a problem as a successor.
It is the chairman who decides the successor.
Isn't this Baek Soo-jeong?
Who's saying this because they don't know that now?
(Edited) No, at best people can say...
That's it
(Juyeon) Be careful, if you go any further you will get wet.
[Sound of fountain coming]
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Exciting music]
Wow
It's a rainbow
It seems like it's been a while since I last saw you
[Calm music]
It's pretty
(Juyeon) Still enough
I like it
Still
Let’s love each other more freely
in front of you
(Juyeon) He did some work.
Baek Soo-jeong
(In-kyung) What’s important about doing a good job?
It's just a target for removal.
I think you did?
Not anymore
When I saw it again, it seemed okay.
(Juyeon) Director Kwon will also like me.
Didn't you say he was like a talented person?
Right?
As expected, I’m the general manager’s style.
I know it well
[lively music]
[Writing sound effect]
(Edited) Um
Are you doing some work?
(Junsu) Who?
This is Director Ban Ju-yeon.
(Edited) Decisions are made quickly
Has good action skills and good sense.
(Junsu) Ah
The team leader in the morning
The person who criticized me for being arbitrary
You look like the general manager.
I guess there are two general managers?
[Nana and Junsu’s laughter]
(Nana) Ah, the former team leader is the general manager.
I thought you hated it
Me too
Ah, where are the likes and dislikes?
All you have to do is do your job well.
(Edited) Huh?
[Keyboard operation sound]
[tired sigh]
[surprised moan]
Ah, I woke up suddenly.
After all, there is nothing like this when working overtime.
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Sound of door closing]
Are you working overtime?
Ah, yes
I went out to work and came back
I have some work left to do.
I think it would be good to finish this
[Keyboard operation sound]
Because of sudden schedule
If you work overtime because you are behind on work,
What happens to my face?
(Juyeon) Stay up late for no reason
Don't go to work
[Sound of footsteps moving away]
no
Telling me to get off work
Who wouldn't be so cheap...
(Juyeon) Oh, and
It's late today too
I don’t think I can leave it to dry.
Just keep your clothes.
Yes? why?
I don't really need it
Because she was pretty
[Soft music]
Clothes!
one piece!
(Juyeon) It’s about one piece.
piece
[laughter]
Funny, really
[Interesting music]
You too, let’s go to my hideout now.
[Blows air]
[Doorbell sounds]
[Sighing] Who are you?
(Shinwon) Panjju, it’s my brother!
[sigh]
(Hajin) My face turns red when I see you
Oh, it really doesn't match.
[Shinwon’s happy laughter]
[Sound of refrigerator door closing]
(Juyeon) To my mother
Please tell me thank you
[Happy laughter]
[Juyeon sighs]
[knocks on the table]
What are you laughing at?
offended
(ID) Me?
Did you laugh?
If you don't know that
How stupid do you have to be?
[Happy laughter]
It's my first time experiencing something like this
(Shinwon) Hey
That destiny
Is it real?
[Meaningful music]
(Young Juyeon) We are destined
My Destiny
your existence
(Edited) Your very existence is so disgusting!
Live forever sealed
The second bottle of this is an otaku!
It's a dangerous situation.
(Juyeon) Be careful
If you carelessly give your heart to a human being
It will be so painful that you will want to die.
you
just now
Did you think about your first love?
[Exciting music]
[Sharp sound effect]
I'll just kill you now without any pain.
[Shinwon’s laughter]
(Shinwon) Hey, you...
[bird chirping]
[Sujeong’s labored groans]
(Edited) Write, is it pretty?
I have no time to wear it and it doesn’t suit me.
[Exciting rock music in earphones]
[sigh]
(Hajin) I’m busy these days because I opened a store.
(main role)
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Message notification sound]
[Interesting music]
finally
(Assistant) As you said
Cleaning completed except for the study room
Yes, thank you for your hard work, go see it.
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[Remote control operation sound]
Oh, that would be nice
(Juyeon) Come on!
Getting ready for your new tomodachi
[ding sound effect]
Shall we begin?
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
[Fast forward sound effect]
[sigh]
(Sujeong) I’m jealous.
something passionately
That you can like it
I think it's precious.
It's not easy to find something you like.
It's not easy to like for a long time
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST-Continued]
So
Feel free to like it as much as you like.
[bird chirping]
[Gong ringing sound effect]
[Door bell sounds]
[Delivery worker’s heavy sigh]
[Interesting music]
[Hajin’s surprised exclamation]
[Delivery worker’s heavy sigh]
(Delivery staff) Check quantity
Just sign it, yes.
(Hajin) Who sent all this?
Black...
Flame dragon?
(Hajin) Ah, yes
(Delivery worker) Yes
- (Hajin) Here
- (Delivery worker) Yes.
thank you
- Oh, good work.
- (Hajin) Yes, please come in. [Door bell rings]
(Delivery worker) Yes!
[Hajin sighs]
[Door bell sounds]
(Sujeong) Sister
What are all the wreaths in front of me?
Uh, what is it?
Why is it so cold?
[humorous music]
What is this again?
(Hajin) Uh, what’s going on?
Without any contact
No, when did you contact me?
(Edited) What is that?
(Hajin) I received a gift for opening the business.
No, who is sending a gift like this?
(Edited) Just looking at the scale, you would think it was a conglomerate.
That's right
[Awkward laughter]
First sit down
Sister, let’s turn off the air conditioner first.
(Edited) Oh, that’s for air conditioning.
I can't save you
(Hajin) Is that so?
[Remote control operation sound]
So who is it?
Stay, friend.
Who are your friends?
Is there a friend I don't know about?
[Serving robot operating sound]
(Edited) Oh, what a surprise!
Hey, what kind of friend are you?
In a store with no customers to serve
Sending a serving robot?
Sister?
Are you a man?
[Fanfare music plays]
[Thumping sound effect]
Black, flame, dragon?
[Interesting music]
[eyes widening sound effect]
Oh my, I guess I shouldn’t come back and throw away the trash.
(Edited) Black Flame Dragon?
Sister!
Have you been in contact with this bastard?
why?
I was deceived by this bastard
Your sister was pissed too!
Yes, but...
You know, him.
Well, I'm good at games
[absurd gasping sound]
(Hajin) Ah, really sometimes...
Sometimes only when fighting
I contacted you sometimes
[Sujeong’s absurd sigh]
(Edited) Oh, I see.
Oh, I did.
[humorous music]
I'll just leave
We should take some time
(Hajin) Ah, strawberry, Sujeong-ah!
Should I throw it all away?
I'll throw it all away
[Hajin’s groans of difficulty]
[Hajin’s powerful moans]
That's enough
(Hajin) Right?
Still, it's a gift
It’s a bit much to throw it away, isn’t it?
Sell it to Altari
(Edited) I hate to see it, but it’s a waste of money
Okay
[Angrily breathing]
(Juyeon) Are you going to work early?
The general manager came early too?
I'm naturally diligent
[light laughter]
[Closes cell phone]
[Elevator arrival sound]
(Edited) Did you check the weather today?
(Juyeon) Yes
The weather is clear today
Low fine dust, medium UV index
The humidity is 46% and the wind is 2m/s.
(Edited) Oh, looking at this
It must be really comfortable
(Juyeon) Yes, it’s comfortable
But if the text is this small
Can you see well?
[light music]
Okay, I can see it well.
This?
(Edited) Oh
(Juyeon) But...
How long are you going to keep doing this?
(Edited) Yes?
[bright music]
[The music slows down and stops]
[Screaming sound effect]
[In-kyung’s surprised moan]
[humorous music]
(In-kyung) Director, are you okay?
Oh, sorry...
Yes, I work
I didn't do that on purpose.
Hey, are you okay?
(Edited) This watch is strange.
High stress level
I'm high too
(In-kyung) I asked them to investigate last week.
What you instructed
Shall I report it to you today?
(Juyeon) Let’s go in and listen right away.
(Edited) What is this?
(In-kyung) Uh, that...
[nervous music]
It looks like a capsule toy?
It's my child's favorite character.
who is in the office
Does anyone have children?
(Edited) No
Who is it?
I left something in the car...
[Sound of running footsteps]
(In-kyung) Yes?
[tire rubbing sound]
[Music that heightens tension]
[Remote control operation sound]
It can't be mine
[sigh]
This doesn't make sense
[Rough breathing]
[dark music]
[heavy music]
Are you late?
That shape, that way
Where have you been?
Ha, ha, grandma...
Who is your grandmother?
(Hyoseon) I have never had a grandchild like you.
He said he would replace my son.
Are you so embarrassed that you forgot the anniversary?
[Crying breathing]
That's not it...
[panicked breathing]
my son
You killed it
(Hyo-seon) My only son!
That day too
Just because of this useless thing
He died!
[Young Juyeon’s trembling breathing]
[Heavy Music - Continued]
I'm sorry
[Young Juyeon’s trembling breathing]
(Young Juyeon) I did everything wrong, Grandma.
I was wrong, I was wrong
I...
Even though I never had a grandchild like you
[shaking breathing]
(Hyoseon) What I’m doing these days
I said it was not trustworthy at all.
But something like this again!
[Amazing elasticity]
This trash
Get it out of my sight right now!
(Young Juyeon) Oh, I’m sorry, Grandma.
Baby, don't do it.
Oh no, no
[Sobbing] I was wrong.
[Heavy Music - Continued]
[Sobbing]
[Young Juyeon sobbing]
[Knocking on door]
(Young Juyeon) Ha, grandma
I was wrong
I won't do that again, Grandma.
grandmother
please take a look
[Rough breathing]
Ha, grandma!
Oh, that's not possible, Grandma.
Just once, grandma
Please look at grandma just once
Grandma don't do that
Grandma! grandma!
[Sobbing] Don't throw it away
Grandma!
Grandma...
I was wrong
I was wrong, I was wrong
[Young Juyeon cries]
[Juyeon’s heavy breathing]
[Sigh of relief]
(Edited) According to Director Kwon,
This is a very expensive deal
Did you say it was rare?
[Nana’s response]
(Junsu) Oh, not even kids.
Who said this to the company, really?
Be honest.
It's Nana, right?
Me?
(Junsu) No, among us
Because I'm still young
(Nana) It’s not me...
Is it you, assistant manager?
[Junsu’s absurd breathing]
(Junsu) Oh, are you crazy?
Ah, a grown man like me
If you like this kind of thing
It's so ugly
[Nana laughs]
- (Edited) Is that so?
- (Junsu) Oh, sure [dark music]
Oh, actually, among my classmates
Is there a kid who collects things like this?
The grown up is still...
Oh, really
Oh, I really don't understand.
Nana, do you understand?
(Nana) Write, I understand...
It doesn't work though
(Junsu) So,
I never, never anyway.
[Loathing moan]
(Edited) Well, I get it first.
Still, we have to find the owner.
Ignorant and narrow-minded
(Nana) Ah, on the company bulletin board
How about uploading it?
Yeah, that will do.
Then this is solved
How much has everyone's report been organized?
(Nana, Junsu) Ah
(Junsu) It's over there, over there
(Edited) Ah, that’s right
That file you mentioned last time.
Wait a minute
What is that?
(Edited) Oh, I picked this up earlier.
Even if I ask around
They said it wasn't theirs.
I have it
I'm trying to find the owner.
Aren't you asking me?
It could be mine
(Edited) Do you have any hobbies like this?
That kind of hobby...
None
(Main role) Baek Soo-jeong
Please return those clothes at that time.
He said eggplant.
Are you talking twice now?
There's nothing you can't do
Baek Soo-jeong also does it.
[dark music]
Now that I think about it, I'm not even a philanthropist.
There is no reason to be hostile.
Ah, I never wanted it
Give me clothes and join the enemy?
No, did I beg for some clothes?
What is so selfish?
Then I can just give it to you.
Because I never wanted it
They say I have a lot of debt to pay off, but it makes money.
Did you even sell it?
Then it would be really appropriate.
I guess that's what I'm doing.
(Edited) The head of the department
Private life you want to hide
I'm turning a blind eye to it.
People in the world know the director’s secret
You should know it all, right?
Are you crazy?
(Edited) Not yet.
I'll bring the clothes to you on Monday.
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[sigh]
[humorous music]
[Embarrassed sigh]
(Edited) Okay, see you tomorrow.
Hello?
I'm sorry, but something came up.
Can I get my clothes back?
I'll give you your money back.
It doesn't matter if you wear it once
(Jjuni Mom)
(Edited) Huh?
On that idiot’s whim
Do I need to spend a few hundred of my own money?
Hey, are you going to expose me and die with me?
no
Let's calm down
What difference does it make if people find out?
I'll be the only one getting sued for breach of contract.
[Moaning with a headache]
[sigh]
[Mouse operation sound]
(Edited) So
[Calm music]
Feel free to like it as much as you like.
What did you expect?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
It's all the same anyway
let's not worry
[Doorbell sounds]
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
You crossed the sea safely and quickly.
As expected, this is the place that Watashi Ban Juyeon trusted and left it to us.
(Juyeon) Yes, this is it
This is enough
[Juyeon’s comfortable sigh]
[The lights suddenly turn off]
[Music stops]
[humorous music]
[Video lecture sound]
I just don't know
[sigh]
Was I this worthless?
It won't work
(Main Role) Career and Skills
I'm calling a trustworthy expert.
Is this me, Ban Ju-yeon’s house?
As someone I never knew
Although it's a little further away than here,
Places you can visit on business trips
A place with too many reviews is also not good.
Because there is a high probability that it is an advertising post.
(Edited) Dad
(Wonseop) Oh
[Wonseop and Nana’s laughter]
[telephone ringing sound]
Oh, wait
[Call button sound]
Ah, yes
[Juyeon clears his throat]
(Juyeon) Are you a first-class hardware?
Oh yes, that's right
[humorous music]
I contacted you because the power outlet went out.
I am in Yonghui-dong. Can I go on a business trip now?
Ah, Yonghee-dong...
Write, ah, that place is a bit far from here.
[coughing sound]
Oh my, isn't it okay?
Oh, no, it works.
It's far away
Oh, let's go, well, well
Oh, it's just a quick ride on a bike.
[sigh]
(Main lead) Instead, the amount is
5 times what you get now
I'll give it to you
[ding sound effect]
[Surprising sound effect]
Can I visit now?
Oh, now?
Oh my, I'm on a business trip to town right now...
It's okay!
me, me, me
Who is this just now?
(Wonseop) Ah, yes, my daughter
Ah, then what
Can we leave right now?
(Juyeon) I will call you the address
Oh no
I'll give you my phone number.
Please text me the address, yes
Okay
It was perfect
[Clears cough]
Hey, you're already busy, give yourself a break
Are you saying you're going to work again?
Hey, they said they would give it 5 times as much.
I'll get in my car and be right back
(Wonseop) Ah, anyway
Oh, let's get some rest at home, okay?
Why did you come here?
(Sujeong) [Sighing] It’s been a while since I met my dad
I'm thinking about going out to eat.
Oh, sorry, uh
Oh, for dinner instead
Let's eat something delicious, okay?
(Wonseop) Oh, and even if it’s nothing special
Be careful with electricity again and again
Dad, go and do it again
Don't help me with this or that
Just something to do
Okay?
yes
[Wonseop’s laughter]
[Interesting music]
Is this Yongseong Palace?
(Sujeong) Wow, it’s different in the way chaebols live.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Juyeon) Suri was seen on CCTV.
Notice that you are being recorded
Unnecessary actions other than repairs
Especially photos and
Video recording is strictly prohibited
How to get to the fault location
I am attaching a photo
Why are you so thorough?
[Exciting music]
It's so good
[Exclamation]
here
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Edited) I will go in when I arrive.
Woman?
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Hello?
What is it?
[Clears cough]
The boss who called earlier was a man?
Oh, I'm the boss's daughter.
(Edited) Don't worry
Because your skills are as good as the boss’s
But, next to the picture
When you press this button
You mean a room is available?
But where did I hear that voice...
[Embarrassed groan]
[Exciting music]
(Edited) Can you at least get an autograph for me?
Accompanying performance
Director?
[Embarrassed sigh]
[Sound of car door closing]
[Interesting music]
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
(Sujeong) You decorated the room really well.
(Juyeon) Go ahead, I'm not a top-class expert
I don't deal with it
(Edited) The image you are seeking
I thought it didn't fit
Hospital?
(Edited) If I were alone
I guess I was out of my mind
(Juyeon) What do you usually do to relax?
(Subin) Head of Department? Is it some?
(Edit) I didn't see it that way, but it's surprising.
(Hajin) Huh?
Black Flame Dragon
(Juyeon) From now on, between us
It may be irreversible